It's cost me $0.07.
That's not too bad.
Yeah, $0.07 to generate one image.
Hand-drawn game sprite of imaging is called--
OK, OK.
So yeah, we need to work on that.
We need to work on the prompt.
We need to work on the input.
I want to be able to generate batches of images.
Also, use the skill to prompt the asset
and to keep the consistency in it because it
should be from the game we want to select to prompt for.
Also, explain to me which kind of sprite
we are going to need if we want to add
those sprites into the games.
And what's the workflow for the next asset management
for the integration to the game directly?
I want to be able to generate a bunch of images,
a swarm reaper enemy lurking forward.
Those prompts are shit.
I like AI generation.
I mean, I can't do that with this generated assets
because the small flies need to be out, but that's sick.
I love it.
So with those pipeline on CI, then we have recursive--
not recursive, but fully automated testing.
So it should improve the quality of the software shipped
because then you have CI and QA quadrills.
I love that.
Because ideal attacking, running, jumping, side views.
Did I pass that?
Or is it at one sprint and reprinted in different--
because yeah, ultra code is really, really nice.
I love AI.
So cool.
It's so easy.
You say which one that you get it.